How to interview friends with specific value,
welcome again, so in today's video
we are again bringing you some very good
stocks which can perform very well and
give you such long
and Jain, I had told you many times in the first video
that this is going to be very good for Chunnat
and sugar, all of you must have taken
entry, then there must have been a lot of profit here,
I told you about the target
and its market is retesting that level right now, so it is
possible that there may be consolidation for some time, there
is a chance of a good turn back in the market and SIM, HDFC AMC,
all the insurance stocks are also performing very well, if
you think that I will help you, then
definitely subscribe to my channel,
like the video and press the button Guru,
next show, I had told you a long time ago that
Axis Bank, if you must have taken entry, you
know, then a reverse entry
drop pattern is forming in it, which will be a
very positive sign for the market, a
good prank lemon for you  This is the
level time in place of more, that is going to be a troubled time,
if you are not sure then you
can check the old one first, if
you have this, I told you to
fold the side here and always keep a stop loss trail,
any panic can
come at any time and the beneficial has
not performed totally, there is a chance that
like tweets, total bank performance, along with the
benefit, there is a chance that a
good move can happen, I hope everyone has
understood, if you have not
taken entry, you are getting a lot of chances here,
if this level spirit, then you have to
take entry, if it does not, then help is needed,
brother, you can get this, bye,
if you told the dream to you, then that buried
bell is weekly time free, I told you
that it is performing very well even above this level in this
question,
you should tell the kid like, if your
entry will rally here, then it will be very
good here, this will be my test target,
but the stock is performing above that also,
you  Consultations can come here
because the volume is a bit low in the scandal,
so positive momentum can come from the moon.
Next, Suman told you about the eclipse
world not done. Let me tell you, there is going to be
time for action here. There were a
lot of SMS messages there, it was getting rejected from the top again and again,
but the stocks are performing.
This is common here. This 22 jigar
line forms 2, so it comes like a pullback, after that the
market gives a positive response,
this is its own platform. So
thank you, here also the form, after that
Sudan raised, all this is common. This
interview is seen a lot. If
you take entry in it, you will all be
in profit. So today the first stock
we are going to see is Rain Industries. If you
use it, the market has just
recovered from a support and this is doing a
beautiful village for the market. Right now, the
advance will be this. If you want to
add by listening, you
can do it till above this. There is nothing much in it, simply the
previous controller for volume is very
high, so chances are on the triangle.  A
request may come or a
brigade will come after some relation at this level, so you have to
take entry in it and
your target will simply be above 463. It is quite simple and less, the
volume is increasing which is a
very positive sign for the friend and the
volume has been increasing in the last three-four days from the famous time, all the
green color for more is showing it to be thick, we are going to
watch it for the next stocks, if we
talk about India about coldness, then this is a good reaction
supermarket place, it is working like support,
if you get interest on this then
you have to take entry on it, if not, I
can buy up Saurabh above hi,
if you can do internal dental dam, the
positivity here is also quite high and the
attack here has reduced and like Christmas, if
we want, we can see different colors and patterns
forming here, in this
also it is quite simple, the volume from the family has been strongly
green trends
for moral momentum since last time and it is
coming again and again from the moon that the
market  Polish remover can give off some
etc. We are going to see less that Car Mill
Limited, I had told you earlier
in this report, let me tell you that if you
get spirits then you have to like it and at this level
you will get research and after that we are
back here in breakfast, we are
seeing that talk of this form has been done,
now you must have folded it and kept it, then a
very good mood can come back in it, there is a
lot of chance, so the glass which we are going to see for you is
Plat X India,
I also told in the video of the day before yesterday and
this level is working as support for the market,
I had told you that this support
works like train racing, I had told you if
you have seen then you can do it further
and this was going to be targeted at the lover, this bag
and I had told you to take entry, if you do, do it
because then according to profit and the next
reversal which we are seeing
came in our eyes, there is a lot of
positive momentum in our market, before that there can be a
retest here, that is a big
position, the volume is also increasing a lot for the market,
that is the chance, this  Momentum
can come, I hope you all liked the
video and you just have to add your voice to it, it is
quite simple and easy.